Right?
What?
Happy day.
It's a happy day, isn't it?
Basically, Miku is the one who talks.
I don't usually run around when we're
together.
I'm sorry, but...
Let's change that.
What?
Change?
So that you can talk today.
Do you want me to talk?
Yes.
Really?
I'm not kissing you.
I'm hungry.
Really?
I'm so hungry.
Tapioca?
It's not tapioca.
There was no tapioca in it.
There was.
Did you put it in?
It was already in there.
Isn't it nata de coco?
No, it's small tapioca.
It's not tapioca.
I drank it.
It's small.
Do you have white tapioca?
I do. It was delicious.
I drank it.
Wait, I'm here too.
Oh, you're here.
I'm digesting it now.
It's embarrassing.
Don't take it. It was my sound.
What?
It was the sound that I should have
sounded at first.
Sorry, sorry. I took it.
Why did you bring the climax in the
morning?
Was it the climax?
Was it a fox?
It was a fox.
Show me.
It's okay.
What do you mean, it's okay?
What's in your eyes?
Dark eyes.
Oh, my God. You've been having a stomach
ache all day.
I started to have a dog in my stomach
recently.
Is that so?
Congratulations.
What's your name?
What did you just see?
Did you see it?
Can you see it?
What?
I'm hungry.
Hungry?
Pajamas look good on you.
But the flowers are different.
Well, the colors are different.
It's not like that.
Isn't it Nanohana?
You saw Nanohana earlier.
We took a walk.
Let's go to the tulips.
The tulip is cute.
I didn't say it's cute.
Why?
I told you earlier.
What is it?
The tulip is cute.
It's beautiful.
Are you satisfied?
Yes.
Are you always noisy?
Very noisy.
You're quiet sometimes, aren't you?
No, I'm talking alone all the time.
Alone.
Yes, by myself.
By yourself?
Yes.
But...
Ah!
Miku, I'm talking to you by myself.
Eh?
Is that so?
Because...
Um...
Recently, Miku and I made a movie club,
right?
Is that so?
I thought so.
A movie club?
The two of us...
Yes.
We gathered in the room once a week and
made a club to watch movies.
I didn't feel like I was in a club.
Did you think it was a game?
Of course.
Then no.
It's okay. Let's do a movie club.
Really?
In the movie club, we can't talk in the
movie theater, but in the movie club, we
can think about various things.
So I'm talking to myself, but I can't get
an answer.
Because you're talking to yourself.
I want an answer. I want to talk to him.
I want to ask him,
You said it, but it's weird that you didn
't say it.
But I've never had a question like that
from you.
Is that right?
No.
Maybe.
Then I'll try my best.
The secret to a long-lasting relationship
like this is to be able to walk together.
Who told you that?
I looked it up.
Really?
Yes.
That's why it's a bow and arrow.
It looks like you're making a mistake in
the distance.
I think so.
You're not wrong.
If you could come with the same heat, it
would be nice.
It's about the movie club now, so it's
okay.
It's not about the movie club.
I don't want to be a burden to you.
It's like an escalator.
It's like...
What do you think I am?
Have you ever been on your own?
I was just born.
No, you're not.
I was born into this world, and I've only
lived a little.
I think you've lived a lot.
How old are you?
About a quarter of my life.
That's true.
You're still young.
You're young, but...
I lost to 4 groups and I'm still number
1.
Aren't you a beginner?
A beginner? A life beginner?
I don't know yet.
How old are you?
I'm 24.
You're 24, right?
No, I'm not!
What did you think?
Didn't you say 24?
23? 22?
Why do you always look like that?
That's right.
Do I look 23?
How old are you? 22?
That's right.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, that's terrible.
You did it, didn't you?
I really don't know.
Make up.
Yes, yes.
I haven't gotten that far yet.
Are you still fighting?
Yeah.
It's weird to be fighting.
Why?
I'm 0 now.
What's wrong with you?
You're 100.
It's not a fight.
Miko is angry.
You forgave me.
I'm still 24 years old.
I don't know anything.
You're younger than me.
It's dangerous.
I have to protect you.
Can you protect me?
You're unreliable.
What is this?
Did you dance just now?
It's a demon.
Let's continue together.
I'm not done yet.
It's annoying.
It's a bed, so let's stop talking about
demons.
You started it.
Where should we go next?
Where do you want to go next?
Where do I want to go?
You said you want to go to Yamagata all
the time.
But I want to go before the tour.
I wonder if I can go.
I don't think you can.
I can't?
Then I'm on tour.
You're on tour.
Well, you can't go.
Is Fukui close to Yamagata?
Not at all.
It's over there.
It's completely different.
Fukui is over there.
I guess I'm a beginner in life.
You were born here.
I wasn't born here.
Yamagata is over there.
Fukui is over here.
Momonga.
Momonga?
The shape is similar.
Fukui?
Fukui is Momonga, Shizuoka is Kingyu, and
Aichi is Niwatori.
That's UFO Catcher.
No, it's not. The inside is a chicken.
No, it's a UFO catcher.
What do you mean by the inside?
The inside is tickling.
The inside is a chicken and goldfish are
friends.
What? I remembered it as a UFO catcher.
I thought there were a lot of animals in
Japan.
But no one said it when I looked it up.
I knew it.
That's right.
Aichi.
A chicken.
Do you know what a rooster is?
I don't know.
You don't know what a rooster is?
My school bought a rooster.
Where? School?
In elementary school.
Rooster and rooster.
Rooster is a little scary.
It's not scary.
Eggs are delicious.
I've never eaten it.
Look, isn't your head amazing?
It's a little scary, isn't it?
Did you buy this one?
This one is more black and more like a ro
oster.
Rooster.
Brown.
This one is really big.
Rooster, chicken and rabbit.
You bought a lot.
What did you buy in elementary school?
Goldfish?
Did you buy it?
It's not a school that can do that.
Was it about 20 people?
How many people were there?
It was too many.
There were 35 people in one class.
I see.
Where did you buy goldfish?
In the classroom.
All of them?
That's amazing.
There was a person like a biologist.
Yes, there was a biologist.
There was a rabbit outside.
It must have been hard for you.
Yes.
That's right.
We cleaned the bathroom a lot.
What kind of club were you in?
What kind of club were we in?
I was the type to go to the school gym.
That's cool.
I was like,
It's a bit different from now.
I think so. I think I've changed a lot.
What are you washing?
It stinks.
I was a little different from that.
I was a bad-looking guy who wanted to
stand out.
What do you mean?
It's an experiment of science.
And it's free.
I want to stand out.
Let's do it.
It was Rika's class, so there was
something like an experiment.
I told you.
What?
No way.
There was something like a flag.
It was a car.
It was like a car that was blown by the
wind.
There was a plastic car.
It was a car that was blown by the wind
and a car that was blown by a fan.
Which one of us will be able to drive the
car with a fan?
Then we decided to try it out.
Everyone raised their hands to the fan.
I raised my hand to the fan.
I was standing in front of everyone.
My body is small, so I thought that Uchi
wa was more suitable for this girl's body.
I was so confused that I lost.
Oh my god.
I know that the result will definitely be
better, but I think I'm the only one who
's different.
It's not cool, right?
It's not cool.
But I think it's good for variety shows.
That's right.
When I went home with my friends, I was
like,
I really knew what was going on.
I can't forget the most embarrassing
thing.
When I go to bed at night and go to bed,
I remember my painful self and sometimes
I feel like crying.
Why did I do that?
Is there such a thing?
Yes, there is.
I don't know at all.
Let's do a cool episode.
What is it?
No.1
There must be something.
What I remember a lot is that I liked
slime.
I looked up how to make slime that can be
made with small things in the house.
I looked up how to make slime, and I
found a way to make sticky slime with a
stick.
Have you tried it?
No.
Really?
I heard that slime wasn't that popular.
In the age of A-chan, squeeze and slime
started to be popular.
When we were in elementary school, it
wasn't popular yet.
So you were in junior high school?
Yes.
I was doing slime when I was in junior
high school.
I think you were a high school student at
that time.
I started doing slime when I was in
elementary school.
You were into slime when you were in
elementary school, weren't you?
We were in junior high school for two or
three years, so we didn't do slime that
much.
If you do slime with a stick, it becomes
a little slime-like.
It's like an eraser.
It's like a history.
I was doing it at school all the time
when I discovered it.
Then it started to become popular
throughout the class.
Everyone started to do it.
I was doing it like I was good at it.
But I was also good at it.
I made a lot of it during class.
Then, there was a mark left on the desk.
The teacher said,
Who is this person on this desk?
We were scolded.
Isn't that cute?
Is it cute?
It's cute.
Really?
After I was scolded, I quit.
That's why I quit.
That's why it's popular in the whole
class.
I'm surprised that you did it.
Why?
Did you have a climbing stick?
What was that?
Climbing stick.
How many do you have?
It's like a climbing stick.
It's like a stick with a green net used
by a baseball club.
There was a stick that looked like a
stick, and I was thinking of playing a
game where I would bounce my back on the
net of the baseball club and go up and
down with momentum, and I was playing for
a long time.
We were playing together, and I thought
it was fun, but I was imitated, and we
had a fight, and in class, it was like a
class room.
There was an hour of class, and one in
the class.
Was it moral? I forgot.
I forgot about it, but for some reason,
the teacher was fighting over something
that we couldn't help it, so he stood in
front of us for an hour and imitated the
teacher and got angry.
I think I've heard of it.
There might be something like that.
I was told to talk to everyone about
which team was the worst.
They stood in front of me for an hour.
Everyone said what they thought.
But I think it's like this.
But there's no one to play with, so I
stood in front of them for an hour.
I felt like I was living my own life.
It's a great life, isn't it?
With this?
I've been living a quiet life.
I know you're an interesting person.
I told you, right? You're a treasure
hunter.
What was it?
I've only heard of it.
Every time I go to school,
Every time I went to school, I had to
write down my address and the type of
paper I was going to use.
I had to write down the type of paper I
was going to use.
The teacher called me in the morning and
asked me if I had decided to move out of
the house.
I answered, OK.
My mother said that if I got the lottery,
I would move out of the house.
You didn't get the lottery.
My mother said that if I got the lottery,
I would move out of the house.
So I wrote, I will move out of the house.
I said it with a serious face.
My mom said it in the house of Atata Hik
osoneguri.
I didn't think I would be treated like a
child.
You are cute as a child.
When I grow up, I will try not to get
depressed like this.
You are cute.
There may have been a painful episode.
This is quite painful.
I don't want to.
You're fighting with a painful story.
What is it?
When I was in kindergarten,
I was in a little runway show in my
hometown of Studio Alice.
I was so happy.
I was so happy to hear that.
When I was a child, I was told that I was
going to be a supermodel in the future.
I often played on the runway with my
kids.
I said, I've walked before.
It's embarrassing to say that.
You're really walking now, aren't you?
Aren't the kids cute?
It's cute, isn't it?
I want to see you when you were a child.
I want to see it.
You've seen it, haven't you?
I bought a lot.
There might be a picture of that time.
Are you waiting for it?
I wonder if it will come out.
Are you sleepy?
I'm not sleepy.
Not at all?
Aren't you sleepy?
Really?
I wonder if it will come out.
Recently, I've been eating a lot. I can't
sleep unless I'm in pain.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
Can you sleep with a full stomach?
Even with a full stomach, I really feel
like I'm going to be a cow.
A cow?
Yes.
You're going to be a cow, aren't you?
Then you should be a cow, too.
What?
Let's buy a cow and live a long life.
Do you want to live alone?
What?
I won't leave you alone.
You want to be a cow?
Yes.
You want to be a cow with me?
No.
I haven't talked to you for a while.
You're so focused.
Yes.
It's like a stamp Miku made.
It's nostalgic.
I'm happy.
I made Ayano's stamp on my own and sent
it to many people.
Did you send it to them?
It's embarrassing.
Yes.
Stop it.
This is around the time I was in
kindergarten.
Oh, this one!
It's so round.
It's too cute.
It's too round.
I used to walk with this face.
It's so cute.
Sometimes I remember it and it's really
embarrassing.
It makes me feel embarrassed.
I think about these embarrassing things
at night.
I close my eyes and think about it.
I feel like I'm going back in time.
Yes, you do.
Do you feel that way?
Yes, I do.
There are no embarrassing things, right?
There are a lot.
I'm sure there are other things, too.
I don't really like to go to bed.
It's not because I'm tired, it's because
I haven't been able to sleep for a long
time.
I see. You can't sleep.
I made a lot of chocolate for Valentine's
Day.
I brought a lot of chocolate to give to
everyone.
On that day, I was beaten up.
Why?
I couldn't sleep.
I was talking to my friends and my mom in
the futon.
I was hiding in there, and I was like,
what should I do?
I was like, what should I do?
We were holding each other's nipples and
we were so shy.
The other day, there was a girl who waved
at me on the way back from the rehearsal.
When we entered the store on the way
home, she was smiling.
With a big smile.
All the time.
You were so cute.
I was about 4 or 5 years old.
And you were wearing a mask and a hat.
You looked like a suspicious person.
You looked at my face and started
smiling.
You were so cute.
What was that?
I was worried.
I couldn't do that.
You couldn't do that.
You were so cute.
I was also a little shy.
But I don't think there's a lot of kids
with older brothers.
I think there's a lot of kids with older
brothers.
She said, don't talk about me, don't say
anything weird.
She said that.
But I think she's probably happy.
I'm not happy.
She said, don't talk about me.
She said that to her friends a lot.
She said, your little sister said
something.
I thought she was a little happy.
Shion is a good little sister like Awa.
I want to sleep more.
I feel like I'm going to fall asleep.
I don't want to sleep.
I want to sleep with you.
What are you talking about?
When we go on a trip, we fall asleep.
You're always so fast.
Don't you want to sleep more?
It's not like that.
The moment we get back from the hotel,
we go to bed.
When we go to bed together,
we fall asleep.
We talked about this earlier.
You really go to bed after 10 seconds in
the morning, don't you?
I'm definitely faster when I'm asleep
than when I'm asleep.
I've been watching TV for a long time and
I've been sleeping for a long time.
No, that's not it.
That's why I'm sleeping because Miku is
asleep.
You're faster when you're in bed.
Yes, I'm faster when I'm in bed.
But I don't fall asleep that much.
I do, but I don't sleep all of a sudden.
Are you fast?
Don't leave me alone.
It's not early.
What are you feeling right now?
Breakfast.
When I go to bed, I think about the next
day's breakfast.
You do, don't you?
Because the next day's breakfast...
There's no time limit for breakfast.
You have to think about it.
What did you eat tomorrow?
Tomorrow's breakfast?
Fried bread.
Why?
We were talking about fried bread
earlier.
I've never eaten it.
I've never done it before.
I'm surprised.
And recently, I've been watching a fried
bread show.
Ready, go!
Buddy!
Why are you so into it?
Buddy...
I've never done it before.
Buddy is amazing.
Can you swim?
I can swim.
I learned it once.
For how many years?
From the age of 3 to the age of 3.
That's too much education.
I don't have a good athletic ability, so
I've been doing other things, but I've
only quit swimming.
How far did you go from the age of 3?
I swam in the air.
That's amazing.
That's pretty amazing.
About the waist of a butterfly.
Can you swim with your back?
I did it at that time.
I don't know now, but...
That's amazing.
Yeah, I was pretty good at it.
I mean, I was doing my best.
But my friends who were doing it with me
...
Yeah.
They're better at it.
I know. Your brother went to Butterfly,
too.
That's amazing.
Miku was always in the beat version.
I'm sorry.
I've been doing it for two years, and I
've always been in the beat version.
The beat version is bad.
I'm sorry. The dimension is a little
different.
I was sad when I saw a child who had not
been taught dancing in a Chinese swimming
pool.
Miku was in the lowest class.
But in the first place, everyone around
me was like,
I can't put water on my face.
I thought I had been learning for two
years, but we were diving together.
In the midst of that, everyone was afraid
to put water on their faces.
I was so scared that I couldn't move for
3 seconds.
But I was able to put my face on.
I was like a king in the lowest class.
Poor thing.
I was just standing there for the rest of
my life.
You can go on a tour with your mom.
You must have only seen your brother.
That's not true.
My brother has tried a lot of things, but
I'm always on the edge.
I grab the poolside and run around.
Then let's do it again.
That's right.
When I went to the pool, I was practicing
with my dog family.
You've been practicing dog pooping all
the time, haven't you?
That's because you're doing that.
No, no, no. I can only swim in dog poop.
Even if I go into the sea or the pool in
the future, I can only do bad dog poop.
But you're good at dog poop, aren't you?
No, I'm not good at it. You took a video
of Aya, didn't you?
It was really disgusting.
It was disgusting.
Why did you do that?
I felt bad.
It's weird.
It's like you're shy.
Shy?
I was just trying to float.
I felt bad because I couldn't float.
Nagi is also a clever person.
I found something I couldn't do.
I want to find it.
I can't move.
I see.
I'm tired.
I was tired yesterday, too.
The day before yesterday?
Yesterday night?
The morning of the day before yesterday?
The morning of yesterday?
I slept alone last night.
That's right.
It's the closest night.
At night.
That was yesterday, wasn't it?
Yes, that was yesterday.
It was the day before yesterday.
I want to listen to it.
Then, can you wear it as it is?
Huh?
What?
I'm doing it.
It's short, isn't it?
I feel bad about this.
Because you can't see it from the back.
I can see it a little.
Did you get told by an art teacher?
When you do this, you can't see the white
one.
I can see this.
I can see it a little.
I can't cut it.
Do you want to do the other side?
Miku has a good head, right?
It's not good.
What did you just say?
There's going to be a lot of episodes.
I was surprised to hear you talk about
your nails.
I wasn't talking about my nails.
It wasn't as bad as I thought it would
be.
I cut it for you, so I thought you were
smart.
I thought it had something to do with it.
You're smart, aren't you?
It's not good.
Is it over?
I just thought you were smart.
It's not good.
It's not good, but...
What is it?
Miku's most beautiful story in her school
life so far is...
What is it?
When I was in the first year of junior
high school, I wanted to make a spring-
like sentence in English.
I was talking about the next seat and
spring.
I thought it was a cherry blossom.
My neighbor said, I don't understand
cherry blossom English.
I said, I don't understand English.
She said, what? It's Cherry Blossom.
I see.
That's amazing.
That was the most embarrassing thing.
The reason I said that was...
When did you say that?
When I was in 11th grade.
At that time, I saw Cherry Blossom as a
special technique of Precure in junior
high school.
I see.
At that time, her face was like, what?
Cherry Blossom?
I didn't know that.
I was impressed.
Isn't that amazing?
I said it was common sense.
You said it was common sense.
That's the most embarrassing thing I've
said so far.
After all, I'll come back later.
Miko is really embarrassing.
It's so hard. I don't like it.
When I auditioned,
they asked me if I had a good head.
I said I had a pretty good head.
You said it yourself.
When you audition,
you don't know what those words mean.
For example, Nagi asked me
if I could be honest.
They didn't ask me if I could keep it
honest.
What did they ask me?
I don't remember what they asked me.
You don't remember?
Do you remember?
I really don't remember.
I don't think everyone asked you that
many questions.
Yeah.
So they didn't ask you every time.
I feel like they did, but I really don't
remember.
I don't think there were many auditions.
Right.
What did you do during the audition?
I did Udetate-fuse.
What?
Did you do it face to face?
No, online.
I played the drums and did what I do
every day for this.
I did Udetate-fuse.
That's cute.
I only trained for a week or two before
the audition.
At first, I didn't have any special
skills, but I liked to eat, so when I was
about to meet my boyfriend at the 4th
screening,
I said, I like to eat from now on, so I
'll eat this ice cream together.
That's cute.
I ate the ice cream I got at home, but I
'm not good at eating strawberry ice
cream, but I can only eat strawberry ice
cream.
I feel like I'm going to kick my feet
now.
Are you okay?
It's dangerous.
Are you okay now?
But I feel like I'm going to kick my feet
all the time, and it's easy to kick these
days.
Be careful.
I just had a runny nose and I had a neck
cramp.
Just before the performance,
What was it?
I had a cramp in the back of my leg.
I had a massage.
I thought I wouldn't be able to come out.
Didn't you know?
At the time of the song of Suitei Shimai,
I had a cramp in the back of my leg just
before Shinjuku Park.
The song was about to end, so I said,
I can't come out.
I was told to lie down for the time
being.
I was lying down and waiting, but I wasn
't there.
I was embarrassed.
I sometimes feel embarrassed when I lie
down and turn around.
I was told to turn around and say,
I cried in a different way.
I want to cry in the sea.
It happens a lot, doesn't it?
And then...
You're talking too much again.
Please talk.
And then...
The strawberry ice cream wasn't that
good.
That's right.
And then...
I was eating it deliciously, but...
The ice cream...
It's delicious.
You're lying, aren't you?
She said,
It's not good.
I said,
It's over.
She raised her bangs and said,
Please look to the side.
Was it embarrassing?
Did you have any reaction?
I didn't have any impressions.
It's over if I show it.
I thought it was over.
I reflected on myself.
It was like a solo version, wasn't it?
I did a slightly different version of
that.
The answer was 46.
I said, it's 46.
And then, my number...
The number I had on my chest was also 46.
I remember being told that I had it.
Wow.
I didn't realize it.
Final assessment?
No, it's different.
It's a little different. It's a little
bit of a face-to-face.
Did you put a number on it at that time?
I was wearing it.
Oh, I remember.
It's like matching the number with a
number.
I like number 1 and 5.
I was thinking about what it would be
like at number 46.
I was thinking that white would be
different.
At that time, I wasn't aware of Nugizaka.
I didn't think about number 46.
I didn't think I was going to be 16, but
I was told that I had realized it at that
time, and I was happy that it was true.
How old were you when you received it?
14?
You were 14 at that time, weren't you 13?
I think I just turned 14.
It's early.
Don't go to bed.
Why?
I can't talk to you.
I can't get up.
Then let's do this.
It's close.
Hey, hey, hey, your feet.
I can't see it.
Saboten!
Didn't you stop working out?
I didn't.
But it's dangerous.
I don't have a lot of weight this time.
I was the last one to work out.
Because I was tall
Oh, you were tall
You were tall
My nickname was Noppo
I can't imagine
Yeah
My pants were so tight
I was too tall
I can't imagine
Yeah
I was called Noppo
Are you always small?
I was in the middle
It was in the middle until the end of the
day.
It's getting in front of me more and
more.
Is your hand cold?
It's warm, though.
My hands are cold.
My feet are warm.
Don't touch me.
Are you going to quit?
Yes.
My feet.
Don't touch me.
A-chan, don't touch me.
What are you doing?
Don't touch me.
I'm sorry.
I'm cold.
I want to do it.
Your hands and feet are perfect.
You're lying.
That's right.
You put your hands out, didn't you?
What?
I guess so.
Because you put your hands in.
Like this.
Then, let's do a group exercise next
time.
It's okay.
Gather your hands.
Have you ever done a burp?
I have.
What?
It's a burp.
I did it.
With five people?
It's an obituary.
I did it!
What is it?
I thought about it.
It's an audition.
It's the last audition of the training.
The staff laughed at us because we were
too unexpected.
You were pretty good at it, weren't you?
I was good at it.
Everyone felt like it was a program, but
we were like,
What is that?
It's an ogi.
It looks like a monster.
What is it?
It's an enemy.
It looks fun.
I'm going in.
What is it?
This is a planetarium.
I remember you saying,
That's Orion's.
Wait a minute.
That's a pyramid of a world heritage
site.
It's like a pyramid of a mountain.
When we were training together,
when we got up,
we heard the sound of the flute.
We heard the sound of the flute.
You were there, weren't you?
You were there.
Yes, I was.
I didn't want to do it.
That's true. But it's okay. It was fun.
I want to do it again someday.
Try writing a script.
Me?
It's nostalgic.
Suihanger?
Manager.
I said the name of the manager who is
really there.
I said, I admire you.
I was like, I'm going to do it, so I was
like, I'm going to do it, so I was like,
I'm going to do it, so I was like, I'm
going to do it, so I was like, I'm going
to do it, so I was like, I'm going to do
it, so I was like, I'm going to do it, so
I was like, I'm going to do it, so I was
like, I'm going to do it, so I was like,
I'm going to do it, so I was like, I'm
going to do it, so I was like, I'm going
to do it, so I was like, I'm going to do
it, so I was like, I'm going to do it, so
I was like, I'm going to do it, so I was
like, I'm going to do it, so I was like,
I'm going to do it, so I was like, I'm
going to do it, so I was like, I'm going
Hang in there.
Are you going to sleep?
See you later.
I can't.
Giving up is important, too.
I can't remember.
I couldn't remember.
I'm so sad.
But this happens all of a sudden.
But I can't tell anyone.
I can't be satisfied by myself.
I know. You'll forget it by then.
Let's watch a video together.
Okay.
By yourself.
Don't go to sleep.
Don't go to sleep, A-chan.
You're going to sleep, aren't you?
I'll wake you up when you're asleep.
Don't come out.
What? You're already in a dream?
I want to sleep.
What do you want to sleep about?
Stop it.
Don't calm down.
There are people like that.
They can't sleep unless they touch their
mother's earlobe.
I can't sleep if I don't touch it.
That's Miku's mom.
Mom?
Whose earlobe do you use to touch?
Miku's.
Do you touch it?
Yes.
Try touching it.
It's cute.
Miku's earlobe is like that.
But my brother's earlobe is bad.
Is that so?
But it's okay.
I want to meet my brother.
You can't.
Why?
I'm in a sleepwalking spot.
What?
Please stop.
I'm in a sleepwalking spot.
What's that?
It's close.
You're always straight when you sleep,
aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You're always straight when you go to
bed.
I try to sleep straight as much as
possible.
I want to look at you and sleep because
you're there.
I don't want to sleep, but I don't want
you to sleep all the time, so sometimes I
can't help but turn my back on you.
Oh, that's what it is.
But...
Why?
When I was sleeping, I was the kind of
person who thought about it in my head
and decided where to sleep.
Rather than distorting your face.
It's not that I don't like it.
Well, that's how it is now.
I used to sleep in the same room as my
mother.
But the bed was different.
There was my mother's bed on the right
side.
I was in the middle.
This is the outside.
I was afraid to turn my back.
To the outside?
Yes.
Yes, that's why I try to keep my legs
straight when I go outside.
That's why I'm here.
What is this about?
It's not about the story.
It's a story because it doesn't have a
story.
That's right.
What do you think the shape of Maya's
legs are?
What do you think it's going to look
like?
I don't know.
I can't sleep with this.
It's okay.
Good night.
It's heavy.
I slept.
Good night.